scrollback.io 2017-03-03

# Privacy policy

### Scrollback Platform Privacy Policy

Scrollback is a hosted chatroom and forum platform developed and operated by Askabt Pte. Ltd., a company incorporated in Singapore. This document is our Privacy Policy, which describes what information we collect and how we use it. This policy applies to all your interactions with the Scrollback platform, whether through the scrollback.io website, Scrollback widgets on other websites, the Scrollback mobile apps or the Scrollback widgets on other mobile apps.

Your use of and/or registration with Scrollback will constitute your agreement to our policy. If you cannot agree to the terms and conditions set forth below, please do not use our services.

#### Goals of this policy

We collect some information in order for you to have an account you can use to participate in Scrollback rooms, and other information that is necessary to make the platform work. Our goal in developing our privacy practices is to allow your participation on chatrooms that interest you, allowing you to remain as anonymous as you choose while assisting the owners of Scrollback rooms fight spam and other forms of abuse.

We this policy strikes a good balance and respects you – our users – who make Scrollback possible. We welcome your feedback — let us know what you think by contacting us at privacy@scrollback.io

#### What Information We Collect

##### Creating a user account

When you create an account, you are required to provide a username and a valid email address. We also record, and retain indefinitely, the IP address from which the account is created. If you sign in using your account on a third-party social network or other website, we additionally retain your unique ID in that website so that we can identify you when you sign in a second time. We do not access any other information or publish anything on external networks using your sign-in credentials.

We also retain your current settings and preferences in order to personalize your experience.

##### Creating a room

If you create a room, we will retain the current settings of the room. Additionally, if you choose to integrate that room with your community’s accounts on other social networks or websites, we will store any account credentials you provide for those platforms as long as you choose.

##### Messages and other content you post

These are retained indefinitely, and their visibility (who can access it) is controlled by the owner of the room to which you post them. Room owners may change this visibility at any time, including making it public.

Private chat messages between users are also retained indefinitely, but they will only be visible to the participants in the private chat.

##### Log Data

Log data is certain information that is automatically collected by our systems when you visit Scrollback, including the history of your activity on Scrollback, the type of software used to access the site (browser, operating system), the address of the external or internal page that referred you, and your IP address. This information is recorded even if you are logged out of your account.

#### How we use or disclose the collected information

Apart from as described below, we will not disclose your personal data to any third parties.

In addition to directly enabling us to provide you service, we may use or disclose your information in the following ways:

##### Improving your experience

All the data you provide may be used to detect and debug technical problems, identify potential improvements, to test enhancements to the service or to prevent abuse and spam. In doing so, we may utilize third-party tools such as Google Analytics. In every such case where a third-party is provided access to your data, we will ensure that these services provide privacy and data security guarantees that match or exceed those in this Policy.

##### Legally required disclosures and emergencies

If we are legally required to disclose your information to the government, we will do so. If we are able to, we will make reasonable attempts to notify you of this disclosure.

Additionally, we may voluntarily disclose your information to third parties under extraordinary circumstances such as to prevent imminent and serious physical harm to a person; to address ongoing fraud, security violations, or spam; or to protect our rights or property.

#### Cookies and client-side storage

As part of the normal functioning of the Scrollback platform, we will store small amounts of data on your computer using “cookies” or “client-side storage”. These may also be stored by third-party tools such as Google Analytics that we use to help improve your experience. These help us identify you when you access Scrollback.

Most browsers include an option to clear and reject cookies and web site data. To discover how to do this, please consult the “help” feature of your web browser.

#### Data Security

Scrollback will make commercially reasonable efforts to secure your information. However, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of this data. You use the service at your own risk, and are responsible for taking reasonable measures to secure your account (such as carefully maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or securing your third-party social network accounts).

#### Change in control

If a merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control of Askabt Pte. Ltd. happens, you will retain the same rights as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy for any reason. If we make changes, we will make resonable efforts to notify you. Where the changes substantially alter your rights, a notice will appear prominently on the front page. Minor changes may only be highlighted by the privacy policy link in the footer of our website.
